thermogenicreviews.com 2012-09-24

# Privacy policy - Thermogenic Reviews

**This privacy policy governs your use of ThermogenicReviews.com (“the Website”), run by Right Spot Media Inc. (hereafter “Right Spot”).**

Right Spot is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This privacy statement applies to the Website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Collection of your personal information

Right Spot collects personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, address and telephone number. Right Spot also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your postal code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Right Spot. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Right Spot for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through the Website, this information may be collected and used by others.

Right Spot encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from the Website so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Right Spot is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content of external websites.

### Use of your personal information

Right Spot collects and uses your personal information to operate the Website and deliver the services you have requested. Right Spot also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Right Spot and its affiliates. Right Spot may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Right Spot does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Right Spot may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (email, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Right Spot may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Right Spot, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Right Spot does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Right Spot keeps track of the pages that users visit within the Website, for such reasons as determining what Right Spot offerings are the most popular.

Right Spot will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Right Spot; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Right Spot; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Right Spot or the public.

### Use of cookies

The Website uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize website pages on the Network, or register with the Website, a cookie helps our web server to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses and so on.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to experience some features of the Website.

Among other cookies, we may use cookies that:

  * Allow third party vendors, including Google, to show our ads on sites on the internet
  * Allow third party vendors, including Google, to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our websites

Users can opt out of such cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp "Network Advertising Initiative"). Users can specifically opt out of Google cookies at the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/ "Advertising and Privacy – Google Privacy Center"), opt out of Teracent cookies at the [Teracent opt-out page](http://www.teracent.com/about-us/opt-out/ "Opt Out"), and opt out of DoubleClick cookies at the [DoubleClick opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/ "Advertising and Privacy – Google Privacy Center").

### Security of your personal information

Right Spot secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Right Spot secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

### Changes to this statement

Right Spot will occasionally update this privacy statement. Right Spot encourages you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how Right Spot is protecting your information.

### Contact Information

Right Spot welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that Right Spot has not adhered to this statement, please [contact us](http://www.rightspotmedia.com/contact/). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
